Four continents. Three kills... Or the love of his life is dead.
Mechanic: Resurrection is a action, crime,
thriller film directed by Dennis Gansel.
Arthur Bishop thought he had put his murderous past behind him when
his most formidable foe kidnaps the love of his life.
Now he is forced to travel the globe to complete three impossible
assassinations, and do what he does best, make them look like accidents.
Arthur Bishop, played by Jason Statham.
Gina, played by Jessica Alba.
Max Adams, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Mei, played by Michelle Yeoh.
Riah Crain, played by Sam Hazeldine.
Jeremy, played by John Cenatiempo.
Mechanic: Resurrection is a 2016 American action thriller film directed by Dennis Gansel and
written by Philip Shelby and Tony Mosher, with a story by Shelby and Brian Pittman.
It is the sequel to the 2011 film The Mechanic, which was a
remake of the 1972 film of the same name.
The film stars Jason Statham, Tommy Lee Jones, Jessica Alba, and Michelle Yeoh.
Mechanic: Resurrection premiered in Hollywood on August 22, 2016, and was
theatrically released in the United States on August 26, 2016.
It received generally negative reviews from critics, but grossed $125 million worldwide
against a budget of $40 million, eclipsing the total of its predecessor.
The film explores themes of assassin, sequel, murder, mechanic, killer.
The tone is intense.